Donald F. Carmony papers, 1949-1984 C4
Indiana University Archives
- General correspondence, 1949-1984; undated
  - H General file (Box 1)
    - Hickam, Mrs. Willis, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Hiller, R.C., 1963 (Box 1)
    - Hines, John W., 1983 (Box 1)
    - Hodapp, Leroy C., 1964 (Box 1)
    - Hoffman, Frank, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Holcomb, R.K., 1966 (Box 1)
    - Hooker, John H., 1964 (Box 1)
    - Hopkins, Jack W., 1976 (Box 1)
    - Hopkins, Dr. James F., 1964 (Box 1)
    - Horrell, Carol, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Horton, Lou Betty, 1983 (Box 1)
    - Hotchkiss, Robert B., 1969 (Box 1)
    - Howard, Stephen H., 1972 (Box 1)
    - Howell, Emma A., 1959 (Box 1)
    - Huff, Robert, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Hughes, John N., 1968 (Box 1)
    - Humphrey, Sen. and Mrs. Hubert H., undated (Box 1)
    - Hungerford, Owen D., 1969 (Box 1)
    - Hutton, Paul A., 1978 (Box 1)
    - Hyatt, Margaret A., 1966 (Box 1)
  - Irons, Martha, 1958 (Box 1)
  - IU Bloomington Library, 1964 (Box 1)
  - I General file (Box 1)
    - Ideal Bookstore, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Ingalls Shipbuilding, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Inlow, Dr. and Mrs. Deprez, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Irrmann, Dr. Robert H., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Jacobs, Harvey, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Jordan, Harold W., 1963; 1966 (Box 1)
  - J General file (Box 1)
    - Jackemeyer, Cheryl, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Jackson, Mrs. Hugh E., 1978 (Box 1)
    - Jackson, W. Carl, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Jarboe, Betty, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Jellison, Dr. Richard M., 1971 (Box 1)
    - Jessup, Kathleen G., 1966 (Box 1)
    - Johnson, Dorothy E., 1966 (Box 1)
    - Johnson, Gerald R., 1963 (Box 1)
    - Jones, Frank, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Jones, Marjorie, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Jones, Sen. Robert, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Jones, Rosalyn, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Jordan, Gilbert L., 1963 (Box 1)
    - Joseph, Marjorie, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Juergens, George, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Kaplan, Herbert H., 1967-1979 (Box 1)
  - Kegebein, Michael, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Kek, Evan, 1965; 1966 (Box 1)
  - Kelley, Darwin, 1962; 1965; undated (Box 1)
  - Kent, Dr. and Mrs. Neil, undated (Box 1)
  - Kinney, Madeline G., 1968; 1969 (Box 1)
  - Kirkagaslis, Basil, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Klinge, Paul, 1957-1977; undated (Box 1)
  - Klotter, James, 1982; 1983 (Box 1)
  - Knoll, Raymond, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Krauskopf, Frances, 1964-1979 (Box 1)
  - K General file (Box 1)
    - Kaempfer, W.W., 1965 (Box 1)
    - Kammins, Jack B., 1952 (Box 1)
    - Kamowski, R.M., 1975 (Box 1)
    - Kane, Dr. John J., 1953 (Box 1)
    - Kaplan, Richard L., 1968 (Box 1)
    - Katz, Dr. Irving, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Keiter, Michele, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Kelley, Ruth M., 1964 (Box 1)
    - Kelly, Daniel J., 1966 (Box 1)
    - Kelsch, Gerald T., 1968 (Box 1)
    - Kenworthy, Prof. Leonard S., 1964 (Box 1)
    - Kiger, Karl, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Kim, Mrs. Dai Sil, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Kimble, Dr. David, 1961 (Box 1)
    - King, Julia, 1979 (Box 1)
    - King, Karen, 1979 (Box 1)
    - King, R.A., 1964 (Box 1)
    - Kinnaman, Dr. John, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Kintner, Dr. K., 1961 (Box 1)
    - Kirk, George E., 1962 (Box 1)
    - Kirk, Samuel, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Klinkenberg, Nancye, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Knoff, Mrs. R., 1966 (Box 1)
    - Kohlmeier, Mrs. Albert L., 1965 (Box 1)
    - Kozacik, Mary L., 1965 (Box 1)
    - Krahulik, Frank, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Kramer, Dr. David W., 1979 (Box 1)
    - Kreider, David, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Krekiæ, Borija, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Krueger, Dr. L.M., 1974 (Box 1)
    - Krug, Mark M., 1963 (Box 1)
      (To Dr. Francis Ianni)
    - Kuhn, Robert J., 1971 (Box 1)
    - Kuss, Mrs. Donald J., 1964 (Box 1)
  - Landreville, Sally, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Lang, Dr. Elfrieda, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Lee, Helen, 1961; 1969 (Box 1)
  - Libby, Dorothy, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Lilly, Eli, 1962; 1964 (Box 1)
  - Livingstone, David, 1960 (Box 1)
  - Lo, Irving, 1976; undated (Box 1)
  - Lugar, Richard, 1967-1977 (Box 1)
  - Lundin, Leonard, 1957; 1962 (Box 1)
  - Lunstrum, John, 1960; 1963 (Box 1)
  - Lynn, John S., 1967 (Box 1)
  - L General file (Box 1)
    - LaFollette, Dr. Robert R., 1961 (Box 1)
    - Lake, Thomas H., 1982 (Box 1)
    - Lankford, Mrs. Kenneth, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Larson, Lawrence C., 1965 (Box 1)
    - Laves, Dr. Walter H.C., 1966 (Box 1)
    - Lawlis, Chelsea, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Lebus, Betty, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Leach, Alexander, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Leiber, Ralph W., 1961 (Box 1)
      (To Robert A. Frederick)
    - Leich, Dr. Charles F., 1967 (Box 1)
    - Leill, Dr. John T., 1965 (Box 1)
    - Lemmon, C.F., 1966 (Box 1)
    - Leopold, Dr. R.W., 1950 (Box 1)
    - Lester, Jennifer J., 1977 (Box 1)
    - Levie, Howard, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Levy, Nathan, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Linback, Carol, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Lindley, Ernest K., 1969 (Box 1)
    - Linkel, Kathryn, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Linton, E.M., 1955 (Box 1)
    - Lloyd, John R., 1971 (Box 1)
    - Logsdon, Eugene H., 1962 (Box 1)
    - Lorton, Ethel C., 1961 (Box 1)
    - Lowe, Robert A., 1963 (Box 1)
    - Lowe, Mrs. Robert F., 1966 (Box 1)
    - Luizie, Mrs. Herman, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Lundgren, William J., 1970 (Box 1)
    - Lundin, Mrs. Beryl W., 1974 (Box 1)
    - Lyle, Charles H., 1971 (Box 1)
  - Madison, James A., 1976-1983 (Box 2)
  - Markle, Carrolle A., 1966 (Box 2)
  - Martling, Mr. and Mrs. W. Lockwood, Jr., 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Maurer, Viola, 1955 (Box 2)
  - McCormick, Gene, 1966; 1973 (Box 2)
  - Meeker, George and Ferol, 1963-1966 (Box 2)
  - Menke, R.H., 1966 (Box 2)
  - Merritt, Lynne, 1969-1973 (Box 2)
  - Miller, Delbert, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Million, Paul E., Jr., 1959-1964 (Box 2)
  - Mitchell, John E., 1965-1967 (Box 2)
  - Moberly, Steve, 1981; 1984 (Box 2)
  - Montgomery, Robert and Pauline, 1960-1962 (Box 2)
  - Mooney, Chase, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - Moore, Alexander M., 1959-1966 (Box 2)
  - Moore, Ann, 1966-1971 (Box 2)
  - Moore, Mr. and Mrs. Powell A. and son Hugh, 1959-1967 (Box 2)
  - Mosier, Martha H., 1964; 1968 (Box 2)
  - Mouser, Evelyn Shipman (Mrs. Sylvan L.), 1964 (Box 2)
  - M General file (Box 2)
    - Maddox, Margaret, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Madeleva, Sister M., 1950 (Box 2)
    - Madigan, Bill, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Madigan, Mary Lou, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Maidenberg, Milton, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Mallett, Dr. D.R., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Mallory, G. Baron, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Manhart, Prof. George B., 1965 (Box 2)
    - Mariani, Peter R., 1970 (Box 2)
    - Martin, Miss M., 1965 (Box 2)
    - Mason, Charles, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Massengill, Phillip, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Massialas, Byron G., 1963 (Box 2)
      See: Krug, Mark M.
    - May, Dr. George S., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Mayhill, R. Thomas, 1966 (Box 2)
    - McCabe, Michael A., 1963 (Box 2)
    - McClain, George, 1966 (Box 2)
    - McClarren, Robert R., 1966 (Box 2)
    - McConnell, David L., 1960 (Box 2)
    - McDaniel, Darleen, 1966 (Box 2)
    - McDonald, Frances, 1976 (Box 2)
    - McGinnis, Mrs. Richard R., 1965 (Box 2)
    - McGuire, Mrs. Ora, 1966 (Box 2)
    - McKee, Donald B., 1964 (Box 2)
    - McKinney, Mrs. Frank E, Jr. (Katie), 1982 (Box 2)
    - McKinzie, Kathleen, 1964 (Box 2)
    - McLary, Kathleen, 1983 (Box 2)
    - McLin, Sylvia, 1961 (Box 2)
    - McMahan, Linda, 1975 (Box 2)
    - McMullen, Haynes, 1970 (Box 2)
    - McMurray, Prof. Floyd, 1961 (Box 2)
    - McQuaid, Mrs. James D., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Meier, Robert J., 1971 (Box 2)
    - Merritt, Jack, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Metzger, D.J., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Miles, Miss Oakey H., 1960 (Box 2)
    - Miller, David M., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Miller, Joe, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Miller, Lorena L., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Miller, Lou, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Miller, Rupert A., 1974 (Box 2)
    - Miller, Dr. Warren E., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Million, Marsha, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Mitten, J. Robert, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Monroe, Kenneth P., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Montgomery, Dr. W.R., 1960 (Box 2)
    - Mooney, Loraine, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Moore, Jane, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Moore, John G., 1963 (Box 2)
    - Moore, Susan, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Morlock, Dr. James E., 1965 (Box 2)
    - Morris, R.S., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Moser, Kathryn, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Mossholder, Robert, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Mueller, Bishop Reuben H., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Mullin, James P., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Munson, Cheryl Ann, 1983 (Box 2)
      (To Dr. James E. Price)
    - Mussio, T.F., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Myers, Rep. Paul, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Najam, Edward, 1964; 1965 (Box 2)
  - Neu, Irene D., 1966; 1980; undated (Box 2)
  - New, Jack, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Nicewarner, Owen E. and Gladys, 1976; 1979 (Box 2)
  - Nichols, Opal, 1958; 1966 (Box 2)
  - Neil, William M., 1959-1981 (Box 2)
  - Nolan, Alan T., 1962; 1963 (Box 2)
  - Nugent, Walter T.K., 1965-1977 (Box 2)
  - N General file (Box 2)
    - Namy, Philip W., 1978 (Box 2)
    - Nash, Dr. Jay B., 1959 (Box 2)
    - National Social Directory, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Neil, William M., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Nofziger, M.D., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Nuckols, Christine M., 1966 (Box 2)
  - Orr, Lt. Gov. and Mrs. Robert D., 1974; 1977 (Box 2)
  - Osborn, Dr. George C., 1955; 1962 (Box 2)
  - O General file (Box 2)
    - O'Bannon, Roert P., 1974 (Box 2)
    - Olive, Borden B., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Olsen, James C., 1964 (Box 2)
    - O'Neill, Jim, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Orr, W.E., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Overmyer, Marvin, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Overton, Dianne, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Owen, Mrs. Kenneth, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Owens, Kathleen B., 1969 (Box 2)
  - Patterson, James, 1968; 1982 (Box 2)
  - Patton, John B., 1977; 1982 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Fernando, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Peak, Philip, 1961; 1974 (Box 2)
  - Peckham, Howard, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Perry, Bernard B., 1957-1973 (Box 2)
  - Perry, Lewis, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Peterson, Margaret Jean (Peggy), 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Phillips, Clifton, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Pitts, L. Russell, 1961; undated (Box 2)
  - Pointer, Clara (Mrs. P.D.), 1950-1966 (Box 2)
  - Price, Charles C., 1949-1950 (Box 2)
  - Prucha, Father Paul, 1965; 1971 (Box 2)
  - P General file (Box 2)
    - Padgett, Bill, ca. 1983 (Box 2)
    - Palmer, Harry, Jr., 1965 (Box 2)
    - Palmer, Linda, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Pantzer, Eric, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Pantzer, Kurt F., 1968 (Box 2)
    - Parker, William R., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Parks, Cameron, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Parrish, Paul A., 1973 (Box 2)
    - Parsons, Claude, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Payne, Lesley, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Payne, Mrs. Wilbur M., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Peare, Robert, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Peden, Rachel, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Peeples, Melvin, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Pence, Judy, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Perry, Rodney E., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Petecher, Mrs. Albert, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Phillips, Norma, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Pickett, William B., 1976 (Box 2)
    - Pierson, Dr. Coen, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Pile, Terri, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Pinnell, Dr. George, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Pittenger, Dr. R.C., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Pogue, David E., 1962 (Box 2)
    - Pompey, Sherman Lee, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Porter, John H., 1962 (Box 2)
    - Potterf, Rex M., 1962 (Box 2)
    - Powell, William, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Power, Samuel, H., Jr., 1978 (Box 2)
    - Price, James E., 1983 (Box 2)
    - Price, Roberta, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Prickett, A.L., 1965 (Box 2)
    - Putzel, Max J., 1967 (Box 2)
  - Quirk, Robert E., 1974 (Box 2)
  - Radelet, Louis, 1950-1965 (Box 2)
  - Rankin, Frank G., 1967 (Box 2)
  - Reed, Doris, 1953; 1965 (Box 2)
  - Rehmer, Rudy, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - Reiberg, Dr. Rufus, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Remak, Henry, 1961-1974 (Box 2)
  - Richey, Robert W., 1960-1977 (Box 2)
  - Ridge, Martin, 1965-1982 (Box 2)
  - Riggs, Jim, 1963; 1964 (Box 2)
  - Riker, Dorothy, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Roache, Esther, 1966-1981 (Box 2)
  - Robb, James, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Eunice C., 1961-1971 (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Warren, 1956-1979 (Box 2)
  - Rodman, Jane, 1962-1964 (Box 2)
  - Rogers, Kathryn (Mrs. Howard), 1953 (Box 2)
  - Rogers, Louise, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Ross, M.O., 1960; 1962 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, John W., 1973-1982 (Box 2)
  - R General file (Box 2)
    - Rabinowitch, Alex, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Raines, Bishop Richard C., 1957 (Box 2)
    - Ramsey, S. (Shein?), 1962 (Box 2)
    - Randall, Dave, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Randolph, Dr. Brady F., 1969 (Box 2)
    - Reeves, Jesse Ray, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Regina, Sister Agnes, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Reichmann, Dr. Everhard, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Reinbold, Charles J., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Reissert, Charles, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Reitan, Dr. Ralph M., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Rich, Claude, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Richardson, Elanna Streeter, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Richardson, Sue, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Richardson, Mrs. Willis, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Riepma, S.F., 1971 (Box 2)
    - Riley, Prof. Joe, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Ripley, Dr. Hugh, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Risinger, C. Frederick, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Risler, Walt P., 1968 (Box 2)
    - Rissler, Herb, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Roberts, George C., 1968 (Box 2)
    - Roberts, Scott, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Robertson, Esther, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Robinson, Debbie, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Robinson, Prof. Robert, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Robinson, Schuyler L., 1960 (Box 2)
    - Rogers, Rep. Michael, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Rogers, Roy, 1951 (Box 2)
    - Ropp, Mary, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Roth, Kim, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Rowe, Charles W., 1979 (Box 2)
    - Rubush, William, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Ruby, Rep. James A., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Rudolph, L. C., 1970 (Box 2)
    - Ruesink, Albert, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Ryshavy, Olive, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Rumsey, Kathry, 1980 (Box 2)
      See: Jarboe, Betty
  - Sage, Leland L., 1967 (Box 2)
  - Schellenberg, James, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Schminke, Dr. Frederick A., 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Schredt, John, 1962; 1966 (Box 2)
  - Schricker, Henry F., 1963-1964 (Box 2)
  - Scobie, James, 1969-1974 (Box 2)
  - Seehausem, Paul, 1958; 1961 (Box 2)
  - Seldon, Betty (Mary E.), 1959-1963 (Box 2)
  - Seward, Fred, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Sheehan, Bernard, 1969; 1971 (Box 2)
  - Shelton, Robert, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Shiner, V.J., Jr., 1974; 1976 (Box 2)
  - Shrum, Wayne, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Simons, Dick, 1954-1980 (Box 2)
  - Sinor, Denis, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Smelser, Dr. Marshall, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Dr. Dwight L., 1963-1982 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Harry M., 1960; 1962 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Johnnie Rutland (Mrs. Henry L.), 1959; 1962 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Willard H., 1961; 1964 (Box 2)
  - Solt, Leo F., 1955-1979 (Box 2)
  - Spencer, Kermit I., 1964; 1968 (Box 2)
  - Stahr, Elvis J., 1964-1969 (Box 2)
  - Starrett, Robert D., 1960-1969 (Box 2)
  - Sudermann, Jacob, 1957-1977 (Box 2)
  - S General file (Box 2)
    - Sacket, Henry R., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Salmon, Mrs. Wayne S., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Sampson, Richard A., 1969 (Box 2)
    - Sanders, Harold, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Scheiber, Prof. Harry N., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Scheick, Dr. Donald, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Schell, Suzanne, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Schmidt, Ms. E. A., 1974 (Box 2)
    - Schricker, Mrs. Henry F., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Schrink, Michael A., 1963 (Box 2)
    - Schultheis, August, 1979 (Box 2)
      (Incomplete)
    - Schultz, Marilyn Frances, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Schurz, Franklin, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Schwilck, Gene L., 1962 (Box 2)
    - Scott, Nellie E., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Selective Service Board, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Setzler, Frank M., 1971 (Box 2)
    - Shafer, Boyd C., 1962 (Box 2)
    - Shafer, Mrs. L.S., 1969 (Box 2)
    - Shaffer, Prof. Robert, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Shake, Curtis G., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Shaver, George F., 1983 (Box 2)
    - Shields, Mrs. Clifford, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Shirey, Warren W., 1978 (Box 2)
    - Shirley, Janet, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Shrum, Edison, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Shulman, Rabbi and Mrs. Albert M., 1959 (Box 2)
    - Shultz, Lawrence W., 1965 (Box 2)
    - Shumaker, Dr. Arthur W., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Shusterman, Alan, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Sikes, P. S., 1963 (Box 2)
    - Simmons, Mark, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Sirmans, Pamela Hughes, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Smiley, Beth, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Smith, Dr. David E., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Smith, Edgar, Jr., undated (Box 2)
    - Smith, Dr. Frederick R., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Smith, George H., 1970 (Box 2)
    - Smith, Harry V., 1960 (Box 2)
    - Smith, Jack, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Smith, Linda, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Smith, Dr. Robert M, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Smith, Stella T., 1963 (Box 2)
    - Snepp, Daniel W., 1977 (Box 2)
    - Snider, R. Nelson, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Snyder, Dr. John W., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Sojka, Dr. Gary, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Spencer, David C., 1975 (Box 2)
    - Spoon, Cathy, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Sprague, Thelma, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Springstun, Bonnie, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Squires, Mrs. Fred, 1963 (Box 2)
    - St. Angelo, Gordon, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Stammer, Lorena, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Stanfield, Mabel D., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Starkey, Dr. Otis P., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Stempel, John E., 1959 (Box 2)
    - Stewart, Barbara L., 1978 (Box 2)
    - Stewart, John L., 1960 (Box 2)
      (To Herman B Wells)
    - Stock, John P., 1963 (Box 2)
    - Stoops, Mrs. James F., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Strain, William H., 1963 (Box 2)
    - Sturgeon, Miriam Meloy, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Sturgeon, Robert, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Sutton, Joseph L., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Sutton, M. E., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Swezey, Burr S., 1963 (Box 2)
  - Templeton, Kenneth, 1962; 1965 (Box 2)
  - Thompson, John, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Thornbrough, Emma Lou, 1960; 1961; 1970 (Box 2)
  - Thornbrough, Gayle, 1965-1977 (Box 2)
  - Thurston, Kenneth, 1964-1967 (Box 2)
  - Treanor, Aline Jean, 1972-1976; undated (Box 2)
  - Tredway, Gilbert, 1961; 1962 (Box 2)
  - Trippett, Byron, 1955-1962 (Box 2)
  - Troyer, Byron, 1963; undated (Box 2)
  - Turner, Lynn, 1963-1966 (Box 2)
  - T General file (Box 2)
    - Taliaferro, Viola J., 1983 (Box 2)
    - Tang, Dr. Peter S. H., 1962 (Box 2)
    - Tardy, Jerry F., 1973 (Box 2)
    - Tarzian, Mr. and Mrs. Sarkes, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Taylor, Joseph T., 1978 (Box 2)
    - Teng, Prof. Ssu-yu, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Thomas, Charles E., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Thompson, Beulah (Mrs. Hale), 1970 (Box 2)
    - Thompson, Jack, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Thornton, Henrietta, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Titus, Mrs. Florence, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Topping, Robert, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Torrey, Prof. Theodore W., 1960 (Box 2)
    - Travis, Cliff K., 1968 (Box 2)
      (To William T. Hornaday)
    - Tucker, Fred C., 1981 (Box 2)
    - Tutorow, Norman E., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Tyler, Robert L., 1961 (Box 2)
  - Ullmann, Harrison, 1965; 1966 (Box 2)
  - University Microfilm, Ann Arbor, MI, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Utley, Bob, 1973-1983 (Box 2)
  - Vance, Russell, 1964; 1967 (Box 2)
  - Vassar, Rena, 1959-1965 (Box 2)
  - Vincent, Steve, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Von Tress, Edward, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - V General file (Box 2)
    - Van Wey, Jean, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Viola, Dr. Herman J., 1975 (Box 2)
  - Walker, Dr. Heber P., 1961 (Box 2)
  - Waller, George, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Watson, Anita Graber, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Weicker, Jack, 1958; 1965 (Box 2)
  - Weigand, James E., 1982 (Box 2)
  - Weintraut, Carolyn, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1953-1983 (Box 2)
  - Welsh, Matthew E., 1963; 1964; 1982 (Box 2)
  - Wentworth, Edward N., 1957 (Box 2)
  - Williams, D. June (Mrs. Tom), 1967 (Box 2)
  - Williams, Edgar, 1955 (Box 2)
  - Willis, Raymond, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Wilson, George, 1976; 1982 (Box 2)
  - Wilson, William E., 1959-1964 (Box 2)
  - Wiltz, John, 1963; 1969; 1977 (Box 2)
  - Windle, John, 1961; 1977 (Box 2)
  - Winther, Mary, 1973; undated (Box 2)
  - Winther, Oscar, 1956; 1965 (Box 2)
  - Wolfson, Lester, 1961-1981 (Box 2)
  - Worth, John O., 1963; 1967 (Box 2)
  - W General file (Box 2)
    - Wahl, H.E., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Wallace, Mrs. Pat A., 1982 (Box 2)
    - Walsh, Justin E., 1979 (Box 2)
    - Warner, Geneva, 1952 (Box 2)
    - Wathen, Richard B., 1969 (Box 2)
    - Watson, Richard P., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Weatherwax, Paul, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Weir, Margaret, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Weisenburger, Dr. Francis P., 1965 (Box 2)
    - Welsh, Kathryn, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Whitcomb, Edgar D., 1971 (Box 2)
    - White, Coletta, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Wickizer, Alice F., 1980 (Box 2)
    - Willbern, York, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Williams, Anne, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Williams, Barbara, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Williams, Brien R., 1977 (Box 2)
    - Williams, Dr. Joyce, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Williams, Ruby, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Williamson, J. Reid, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Wilson, Mr. and Mrs. Absalom Wilson, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Wilson, Robin, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Wilson, Theodore, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Winchell, Barney Y., 1965 (Box 2)
    - Winther, Mary, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Wolf, Paul H., 1959 (Box 2)
    - Woodford, Frank B., 1961 (Box 2)
    - Wyant, Marcia, 1966 (Box 2)
  - X-Y-Z General file (Box 2)
    - Yahl, Daniel R., 1959 (Box 2)
    - Yaryan, Bill, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Yitman, Gerald C., 1980 (Box 2)
    - Yoder, Dr. Paton, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Young, Dr. John J., 1951 (Box 2)
    - Young, Richard David, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Young, Dr. Theodore Alfred, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Youngs, Elodia, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Zarabsky, Dorothy G., 1966 (Box 2)
    - Zarria, Virginia, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Zenor, Carl A., 1964 (Box 2)
    - Zimmer, Donald, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Zook, Max D., 1955 (Box 2)
  - Unknown, 1968; 1969; undated (Box 2)
- Indiana University, 1955-1984
  - History Department, 1955-1984; undated
    - Administrative structure, 1958-1974 (Box 2)
    - Audio-visual user's guide, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Course evaluations, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum changes, 1959-1980; undated (Box 2)
    - Departmental meeting minutes (Box 2)
      - 1955-1959 (Box 2)
      - 1960-1966, 1969 (Box 2)
      - 1970-1979 (Box 3)
      - 1980-1983 (Box 3)
    - Departmental review, 1973; 1977; undated (Box 3)
    - Enrollment figures, 1956-1984 (Box 3)
    - Faculty and annual reports - Ft. Wayne Extension, 1940-1944 (Box 3)
    - Faculty annual and summary reports, 1958-1981 (Box 3)
    - Grade distributions, 1955-1958 (Box 3)
    - Graduate and post-doc materials, 1955-1981; undated (Box 3)
    - Graduate student financial aid, 1973; 1975 (Box 3)
    - Graduate students pending, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
    - H105 and H106 - T.A. meeting, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Historic preservation degree at Ball State, 1979; 1981 (Box 3)
    - Interdepartmental communication and memos, 1955-1982; undated (Box 3)
    - J331 - Outline and correspondence, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Job placement for doctoral students, 1964-1975 (Box 3)
    - Masters program at IUPUI: (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 3)
      - New Degree Program request (Box 3)
        - 1979 (Box 3)
        - 1982 (Box 3)
    - Report on transfer of American Historical Review to IU, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Student Questionnaire responses, 1967; 1968 (Box 3)
    - Undergraduate program materials, 1962-1978 (Box 3)
  - History Department committees, 1957-1983; undated
    - Advisory Committee, 1968-1979 (Box 3)
    - Economic History Project Committee, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee meeting minutes (Box 3)
      - 1957-1962 (Box 3)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 3)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 3)
      - 1970-1983 (Box 3)
    - Fellowship and Assistantship Committee, 1963-1981 (Box 3)
    - Field Committee, 1970; 1982 (Box 3)
    - Graduate Program Committee, 1958-1979; undated (Box 3)
    - Honors and Faculty Priorities Committee, 1973; undated (Box 3)
    - Journal of American History Search Committee, 1962-1978 (Box 3)
      [Restricted - in Box 5]
    - Long-range Planning Committee, 1958-1980 (Box 3)
    - Policy Committee meeting minutes, 1962-1977 (Box 3)
    - Priorities for Faculty Recruitment Committee, 1962-1975 (Box 3)
    - Salary Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 3)
    - Search Committee, 1958; 1975-1976 (Box 3)
    - Undergraduate Program Committee, 1959-1968; undated (Box 3)
  - IU committees, 1957-1982; undated
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee, 1972-1974; undated (Box 3)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee - Correspondence with Brian Bex, American Communications Network, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
    - American Studies Committee, 1965-1977 (Box 3)
    - Faculty-Student Liaison Committee, 1957-1970; undated (Box 3)
    - Graduate service to State Parks committee, 1961-1962 (Box 3)